John W. Warner papers MSS 10191
University of Virginia, Special Collections Dept.
- John Warner papers (-by accession), 1970-2007; MSS 10191_by; 713 Cubic Feet Cubic foot boxes; This collection consists of 712 cubic foot boxes.
  - Dept. L: Congressional Fellow Files, 1/1/1992-12/31/1992 (Box 337)
    Nottaway County; Blackstone Army Airfield; Downtown Site, Proposal Submitted by the City of Richmond, Office of Economic Development, 5/29/1992 [binder]; Southern Gateway Site, Proposal Submitted by the City of Richmond, Office of Economic Development, 5/29/1992 [binder]
  - Dept. L: Congressional Fellow Files, 1/1/1992-12/31/1992 (Box 338)
    CPT Zebrowski, Appender "Whistle Blowing"; Army Prosthetics Issue, 1/1992; NAVSEA Drawdown; Misc Aug '92; Misc Oct; Misc 3/1992; Misc-12/1992; 7/1992-Misc; RCI State Dept Grant w/ Russia, Aug '92; Newport News Econ Develop.; Misc 5/1992; Untitled Envelope: Clippings; ILT John M. Sheckler, 228-06-0466; 50th Anniversary of World War II; VA. Trip, 3 Aug-3 Sept; Paul Vandermyde, VSE; April 1992-Miscellaneous; 2/1992-Miscellaneous; 6/1992-Miscellaneous; Nottoway; UXB-Rich Dugger, John Boyden; Vinnell Corp.; Perpetual Freedom, Joanne Vecchinnoe, 1/1992; Relief Operations; Misc Sept 92; County of Nottaway, Virginia [binder]; Midway, Battle of; 1/1992 - Miscellaneous; Misc Nov 92; Seay, Captain Marvin E., USN, Navy, 1991
  - Dept. A: JW Personal Records, 1/1/1990-12/31/1992 (Box 339)
    1990 Trip File; Personal: Trip '92, back up, Tickets, etc.; 11 License Plates from Virginia and Congress
  - Dept. A: Scheduling/Invites, 8/1/1988-9/11/1988 (Box 340)
    1988 Republican National Convention Caucus Teams Briefing Book [binder]; 41 envelopes in chronological order by date
  - Dept. A: Scheduling files, 5/1/1989-6/15/1989 (Box 341)
    46 envelopes in chronological order by date
  - Dept. A: Master schedules, 1/1/1989-12/31/1991 (Box 342)
    1989 Master Scheduling Log, January - June [binder]; 1991 Master Schedule Jan. thru May Book 1 of 2 [binder]; 1990 Schedule [binder]
  - Dept. A: Schedules, 1/1/1987-12/31/1992 (Box 343)
    Month at a Glance Administrator 1989 [October - December] [notebook]; Month at a Glance Administrator 1989 (January - September) [notebook]; Month at a Glance Administrator 1988, October - December [notebook]; 7/1992 thru 12/1992 [binder]; Month at a Glance Administrator 1988 January - September [notebook]; Month at a Glance Administrator 1987 [notebook]; 1/1992 thru 6/1992 [binder]
  - Dept. C: Recommendations Files A-M, 1/1/1990-12/31/1994 (Box 344)
    118 folders of recommendations, arranged alphabetically by last name
  - Dept. A: Scheduling Logs, 7/1/1986-12/31/1990 (Box 345)
    Master Log January to July 1988; Senator's Log July to December 1989; Senator's Log July to December 1988; Master Schedule Log July to December 1988; Senator's Log January to June 1989; Senator's Log 1/1988; Master Log July to December 1986; Master Log 1990
  - Dept. A: Congressional voting record, 1/27/1988-11/30/1989 (Box 346)
    Record Vote Analysis 101st Congress, 1st Session [binder]; 100th Congress 2nd Session, 200 Congress [binder]; 100th Congress 2nd Session, Record Vote Analysis, 1-199 [binder]
  - Dept. A: Cong. Vote record and Senator legislative work, 1/1/1985-12/31/1987 (Box 347)
    Record Vote Analysis- 99th Congress 1st Session [binder]; 100th Congress: Record Vote Analysis 1-199 [binder]; Congressional Record- Senate [binder]; 100th Congress: Record Vote Analysis 1st Session #200- [binder]
  - Dept. A: Scheduling/Invites Accepted, 5/1/1996-8/31/1996 (Box 348)
    123 folders in chronological order by date
  - Dept. A: Statue of Liberty- Zumut Atoka County Supper Files, 8/1/1978-10/21/1986 (Box 349)
    Atoka Country Supper; Atoka Country Supper, Sept. 19/1981; Statue of Liberty/Ellis Island foundation; Tenneco Inc.; Atoka Country Supper; Atoka Country Supper, Sept 13/1980
  - Dept. L: 102nd Congress files - Energy, 1/1/1991-12/31/1992 (Box 350)
    Toxic Substances Subcommittee Hearing on Lawn Chemicals, 5/9/91; S. 225-- Fredericksburg & Spotsylvania County Battlefields National Battlefield Park Expansion Act [presentation folder]; 102nd Congress: ANWR Debate [presentation folder]; S. 1220 -- National Energy Security Act, General Information [presentation folder]; Appomattox River Water Authority Hydroelectric Project; National RADOR Action Week Resolution (10/18/1992) [presentation folder]
  - Dept. L: 102nd Congress files - Energy, 1/1/1991-12/31/1992 (Box 351)
    102nd Congress - EPW, FULL COMMITTEE/SCIENCE ADVISORY BOARD 1/24/91; RCRA: 9/11/91 Hearing, Special Wastes: Oil Mining; Congressional Record, No. 142- Part V, Proceedings and Debates of the 102nd Congress, 2nd Session [book]; Yorktown Battlefield- Filming; Hanford Clean Up - ICF; Energy: Science & Technology Bill; CONSOL- Coal Thermal Dryer; George Mason Memorial Resolution, Senate Resolution 219
  - Dept. L: Commerce, Armed Services, Banking, and Budget Committees, 1/1/1992-12/31/1992 (Box 352)
    1992 Commerce, January - June [presentation folder]; 1992 Armed Services, July - August [presentation folder]; 1992 Armed Services, September - December [presentation folder]; 1992 Banking [presentation folder]; 1992 Budget [presentation folder]; 1992 - Commerce, July - December [presentation folder]; ARM, January - June 1992 [presentation folder]
  - Dept. L: Appropriations and Agriculture Committees; speeches made by Senator Warner, [Pass-through letters to other agencies and responses to individual constituent questions/concerns], 1/1/1992-12/31/1992 (Box 353)
    1992 Appropriations, July - December [presentation folder]; 1992 Administration [presentation folder]; 1992 - Speeches/ Floor Statements [presentation folder]; 1992 Agriculture [presentation folder]; 1992 - Appropriations, January - June [presentation folder]
  - Dept. A: Accepted invitations, 1/5/1996-4/30/1996 (Box 354)
    112 folders of invitations and schedules filed by date of event.
  - Dept. A: Rec. Letters L-Z, 1/1/1990-12/31/1990 (Box 355)
    Recipe-1990; Untitled Folder: Biography of Senator Warner (multiple copies); Condolences; Anniversary; 5 untitled folders of recommendations; Front Office Info; Recipes; Birthday; Retirement; Autographed Color Photograph of the Senator; Congratulations; Greetings; Blue Forms; 106 folders of recommendations, arranged alphabetically by last name (L-Z); Eagle Scout; Animal Rights
  - Dept. L: Margot Smith endorsement and animal rights, 10/5/1990-3/31/1993 (Box 356)
    Endorsements- Waiting on Response ;Senate Tourism Caucus; Untitled Folder: Silver Spring Monkeys; Untitled Folder: Pet Stores (includes cassette: Fruchter with Laufer 4/29/92); Animal Rights Issues; Endorsements to do (empty); Misc. Letters sent 1991; Endorsements- Waiting on Response, 1992; Endorsements- Done 91; Combined Federal Campaign; Miscellaneous. To Do; Silver Spring Monkeys; Miscellaneous Letters sent 1992; Endorsements- Pending, 1993; Pending Requests- CRS, LIBE; Endorsement Responses; Animal Rights; Misc. Letter, 1993; Loose Paper: Flag Request forms, Legislative material; Animal Rights; RECS- Holding; Endorsements- Done 1992; 1992 Phone Call Reports; To Be Filed; Animal Rights (ARW), 1991-1992; Animal Rights 1990
  - Dept. A: Scheduling/Invitations Accepted, 1/1/1993-4/28/1993 (Box 357)
    118 envelopes in chronological order.
  - Dept. A: Scheduling/Invitations Accepted, 4/29/1993-5/31/1993 (Box 358)
    33 envelopes in chronological order by date
  - Dept. A: Scheduling/Invitations Accepted, 9/1/1996-12/31/1996 (Box 359)
    122 folders in chronological order by date. Nov and Dec. folders are all empty.
  - Dept. A: Scheduling/Invitations Accepted, 6/20/1988-7/31/1988 (Box 360)
    42 envelopes in chronological order
  - Dept. A: Scheduling/Invitations Accepted, 6/1/1988-6/19/1988 (Box 361)
    20 envelopes arranged chronologically
  - Dept. A: Scheduling/Invitations Accepted, 1/1/1991-6/30/1991 (Box 362)
    114 envelopes in chronological order. Missing April and May files.
  - Dept. A: Scheduling/Invitations Accepted, 3/26/1991-5/31/1991 (Box 363)
    67 envelopes in chronological order
  - Dept. A: Scheduling/Invitations Accepted, 6/16/1989-7/31/1989 (Box 364)
    48 envelopes in chronological order
  - Dept. P: Dominion Media Service Co. Press Clippings, 10/1/2002-11/30/2002 (Box 365)
    41 packets of loose press clippings arranged chronologically by date, also empty folders
  - Dept. P: Senator Warner Mentions in Press Clippings, 1/1/1988-12/31/1988 (Box 366)
    11/98; 3/1988 Mentions; 12/98; 6/1988 Mentions; 5/1988 Mentions; 7/1988 Mentions; 2/1988 Mentions; Clips 9/1998; 8/1998; 1/1988 Mentions; 10/1998; 4/1988 Mentions
  - Dept. P: Dominion Media Service Co. Clippings, newspapers, 4/11/1999-11/30/2001 (Box 367)
    Richmond Times Dispatch, Sunday 4/11/1999 [10 copies entire newspaper]; 20 packets of clippings from Dominion Media Services, September - 11/2001; each packet holds part of a month, several different packets for each time period.; Senator John Warner Key Word Master List, 11/27/2001
  - Dept. P: Dominion Media Service Co. Clippings, 5/1/2001-12/31/2001 (Box 368)
    32 folders of clippings from Dominion Media Service Co., each folder holds part or all of a month.
  - Dept. P: 30 Videotapes, Senator John Warner Interviews, [no dates given] (Box 369)
    McNeil/Lehrer 2-21-95: 02/22/95 [VHS]; Fox Morning News, 3/12/93 [VHS]; Floor Statement with Comments By Nunn and Sasser, 4/8/1992 [VHS]; McNeil/Lehrer 10/31: 11/01/94 [VHS]; McNeil/Lehrer 2-21-95: 02/22/95 [VHS]; Fox Morning News (11/10/94), 11/10/94 [VHS]; McLauglin One/One & Group: 06/06/94 [VHS]; ABC, NBC, & CBS: 01/27/94 [VHS]; Face the Nation 1/30/94; CNN Late Edition 1/29/94 [VHS]; PBS McNeil/Lehrer: 05/11/95 [VHS]; Prime Time Live: 09/29/94 [VHS]; NBC News, For McNeil/Lehrer 11-1: 9/29/94 [VHS]; Nightline, Face the Nation, Late Edition, & Fox Evening News: 01/31/94 [VHS]; McNeil/Lehrer (Tuesday): 05/09/95 [VHS]; ABC World News Tonight - 1/25/1993: 01/25/93 [VHS]; McNeil/Lehrer (11/07/94): 11/09/94 [VHS]; CNN Larry King: 06/28/94 [VHS]; 2 untitled VHS; Nightline 29 minutes: 1/28/94 [VHS]; ABC, NBC, CBS: 01/27/94 [VHS]; ABC Nightline For 10/18/1994: 10/19/1994 [VHS]; Prime Time Live ABC: 1/11/91 [VHS]; Larry King Live: 12/07/24 [VHS]; Fox Morning News Segment, 5/10/94 [VHS]; Armed Services; Bill - Keep: 02-09-95 [VHS]; CNN Larry King: 05/01/95 [VHS]; CNBC: 01/31/95 [VHS]; Fox Evening News: 01/27/94 [VHS]; Larry King Live: 5/10/93 [VHS]; Inside Politics, Larry King: 01/26/94 [VHS]
  - Dept. P: Dominion Media Service Co. Clippings, 10/22/2003-12/7/2003; 1/1/2004-12/31/2004 (Box 370)
    142 packets of clippings from Dominion Media Service Co., each packet holds part of a month, several different packets for each time period.
  - Dept. P: Press Clippings, 4/1/2002-9/30/2002 (Box 371)
    119 packets of press clippings (Apr-Sept), arranged by date
  - Dept. P: Dominion Media Service Co./Local Press Clippings, 1/1/2003-1/31/2004 (Box 372)
    John Warner United States Senator; 96 packets of press clippings (1/2003-1/2004), arranged by week; Loose Papers: clippings, notes, correspondence, reference materials; McLaughlin & Associates
  - Dept. P: Form Letters, 1/1/1979-12/31/1989 (Box 373)
    Library Item Encyclopedia 1-400 (form letters/issue mail) [binder]; Library Item Encyclopedia 401-825 (form letters/issue mail) [binder]
  - Dept. P: Transcripts, 1/1/1985-12/31/1989 (Box 374)
    Transcripts September--12/1989, arranged chronologically by date [binder]; Library Items 801+ (form letters/issue mail) [binder]; Transcripts January--8/1989, arranged chronologically by date [binder]
  - Dept. P: Non-indexed Press materials, 1/1/1997-12/31/2001 (Box 375)
    4th Circuit; VA Tech Speech Drafts; Untitled Folder: Statements and Maps, 1999-2001; NNS-Gen Dynamics '99; Press Releases and Notes [portfolio folder]; Norfolk Speech Prep, 8-6-2001 [portfolio folder]; 2 Untitled Binder: Agriculture; Founders Day 2000, Presidential Installation Ceremony, 4/28/2000 [program]; Loose Papers: Statements, Memos, Schedules, and Clippings, 1997-2000; Richmond Times-Dispatch Anniversary Edition, Sunday, 10/15/2000 [newspaper]; 99 Water Resources; J.W. File
  - Dept. P: Press Clippings, 6/26/1997-3/28/2002 (Box 376)
    ISTEA; Partial Birth/Abortion; 52 clipping packets from 12/22/2001 to 3/28/2002, by individual dates, some clippings organized by subject; Log Cabin Rep.
  - Dept. P: Dominion Media Service Co. Press Clippings, 1/1/2002-9/30/2002 (Box 377)
    110 individual packets of clippings joined together by rubber bands. Grouped by weeks
  - Dept. P: Miscellaneous Press Clippings, 9/1/1990-1/1/1991 (Box 378)
    7 folders of press clippings in random order. Clippings inside folders are arranged somewhat in chronological order by date
  - Dept. P: Miscellaneous Press Clippings, 11/1/1989-8/31/1990 (Box 379)
    Untitled folder: clippings from 11/89 to 12/89 in backward ascending order; Untitled folder: clippings from 6/90 to 8/90, in somewhat chronological order
  - Dept. P: Miscellaneous Press Clippings, 10/1/1989-6/25/1990 (Box 380)
    6 Folders with misc press clippings in random order. Clippings in folder are arranged chronologically by date
  - Dept. P: Interview and Speech Tapes, 1/1/1969-12/31/1969 (Box 381)
    Microphone Box, mostly empty, with single male-to-female jack; E. P. Stafford (Reel]; Quantico Grad School Speech, 6/4/1969 [Reel]; 27 floppy disks (9 inch): Transcripts, Speeches, Announcements, News Releases; Swearing-In of Mr. Warner, 2/11/1969 [Reel]; 4 Untitled Reels
  - Dept. P: Press Clippings, 9/1/1988-12/31/1998 (Box 382)
    24 packets of press clippings (Sept-Dec), arranged by date
  - Dept. P: Press Clippings, 7/1/1998-12/31/1998 (Box 383)
    34 packets of press clippings (Jul-Dec), arranged by date
  - Dept. P: Press Clippings, 7/1/1988-11/30/1988 (Box 384)
    Roll Call, Monday, 9/14/1998 [newspaper] (4 copies); 31 packets of press clippings (July-Nov), arranged by date
  - Dept. P: Miscellaneous Press, 1/1/2001-12/31/2002 (Box 385)
    To-Carter; Clippings; Loose Papers: Notes, Clippings,; Time, 10/1/2001 [magazine]; Campaign Stuff; Photographs; Speech Backup; The No Child Left Behind Act, Op-Ed by U.S. Senator John W. Warner; Hampden Sydney College Commencement-Remarks, 5/12/2002; Virginia Is For Lovers [bumper sticker]; The Philippine Scouts, Centennial 1901-2001; War College; Culpeper Agenda; United States Senate [portfolio folder]; John Warner, United States Senator [portfolio folder]; Ballpoint pen; Handwritten notes on index cards; Richmond Times-Dispatch, Sunday, 9/8/2002 [newspaper]; Pocahontas Parkway: The Greater Richmond Connector [portfolio folder]; Notebooks with handwritten notes; Photographic Negatives [binder]; Federal Provider Directory
  - Dept. P: Press Releases and Schedules, 1/1/1991-12/31/1992 (Box 386)
    Untitled Binder: 1992 Press Releases arranged in reverse chronological order by date; Untitled Binder: 1991 Press Releases arranged chronologically by date; January-June 1992 Schedules [binder]
  - Dept. P: Press Releases, 1/1/1993-12/31/1994 (Box 387)
    1994 Press Releases [binder]; Untitled Binder: 1995 Press Releases, arranged in reverse chronological order by date; 1993 Press Releases [binder]
  - Dept. P: Press Release Clippings Books, 1/1/1979-12/31/1984 (Box 388)
    Untitled Binder: 1984 Press Clippings, arranged by subject; Press Releases 1979, arranged in reverse chronological order [binder]
  - Dept. P: Press Release Book, 1/1/1980-12/31/1982 (Box 389)
    Press Releases 1980, arranged in reverse chronological order [binder]; Press Releases 1982, arranged in reverse chronological order [binder]; Press Releases 1981, arranged in reverse chronological order [binder]
  - Accepted Invitations, 4/1/2001-6/30/2001 (Box 390)
    91 folders arranged chronologically
  - Accepted Invitations, 8/1/1990-12/31/1990 (Box 391)
    153 folders arranged chronologically within months
  - Office Manager Files and Senator's Letters, 1/1/1999-12/31/2000 (Box 392)
    Leadership Institute; Sergeant at Arms Information; 10/2003; Government Printing Office 2000; Bring Your Child to Work Day; Decatur House; 1993 Senate Security; Federal Emergency Mgmt. Agency (FEMA); Directories/Information Guides; Copier Information; 1993 Sergeant at Arms Office; Franked Mail/Mass Mailing 2000; U.S. Senate Health Promotion; 2/2003; 11/2003; Heritage Foundation; 9/2003; Employee Assistance Program; 1/2003; Copier; 5/2003; American's With Disabilities Act; Job Descriptions; Intern Lecture Info; 7/2003; CFC Campaign 1999/2000; 12/2003; Computer Center; Bar Admission Recommendations; White House 2003; 3/2003; 1993 Legislate; NUTS; 8/2003; Family Medical Leave Act Information; Form Letter-Samples; 6/2003; 4/2003; 1993 Inventory; Financial Disclosure 1999/2000; Loose Papers: Requests for Materials, memorandum, calendar, fax coversheets; 1993 Joint Committee on Printing; 1993 Rules Committee; 1993 Library of Congress
  - Office Manager Files, Miscellaneous Information Files, Mass Mailing, and Presentations, 1/1/1991-12/31/1995 (Box 393)
    Mass Mailing 1992; General Correspondence; Human Resources Info System; Loose Papers: Records of Permanent Historical Value (2 copies); 1993 U.S. Senate Employment Practices: A Study of Staff Salary, Tenure, Demographics and Benefits [publication]; Library of Congress 1992; Congressional Management Survey; 1994-1995 Ethics Committee; Unclaimed Recommendation Responses; Post Office Information; Congratulations Letters & Information; Homosexuals in the Military: Policies and Practices of Foreign Countries (2 copies); SOAS; District Office - GSA: General, 1991; Constituent Requests (Misc.); Thank You letters; Office Manager Meetings; Internet Messages; Internet Information; 1994-1995 Directories/Authorizations; Fair Employment Practices; Financial Disclosure; Office Expense Account 1992; Legi-Slate 1992; Speeches-1991; Family Medical Leave Policy
  - Office Manager Files, 1/1/1994-12/31/1995 (Box 394)
    Loose Papers: Senator John Warner Correspondence; Staff Manual; 1994-1995 Post Office; Lexis-Nexis; Superintendents Office; Sexual Harassment Policy; 1994-1995 Joint Committee on Printing; 1994-1995 MAPs- Capitol, etc.; 1994-1995 Rules Committee; RespecTeen National Youth Forum; Intra-net; Presidential Classroom; Nut; U.S. Senate Youth Program; 1994-1995 Senate Security; 1994-1995 Recommendations Personal; 1994-1995 Sergeant at Arms Office; 1994-1995 Library of Congress; 1994-1995 Service Department; Congressional Youth Leadership Council; Student Programs; Senate Steering Committee; Quality Assurance Control; Recommendations Fed Employees; Recommendations Former Interns
  - Stewart Verdery Files, 1/1/1996-12/31/1996 (Box 395)
    Untitled presentation folder: Contains correspondence, reference materials regarding OSHA; Team Act; Volunteer Firefighters; Arlington County; Labor-Rail Strike; General-Clinton Scandals; Campaign Miller Charges; General D.C. Legal; Right to Work; General Minority Issues; Campaign Miller Suit; Labor-Minimum Wage-Prisoners; National Right to Work Act S.581; Minimum Wage; General Scorecards; Letters; Alexis Herman; Labor Committee [presentation folder]; Labor-Single Location; Labor-S.1423-OSHA [presentation folder]
  - Office Manager Files and Press Clippings, 7/15/1980-4/7/2008 (Box 396)
    1980 Republican National Convention, Detroit, Michigan, 7/15/1980; Congressional Award Information, Correspondence and Reference Information, 1995-1999; SOAS 99; Loose Papers: Clippings - Thrift Industry's Biggest Group to Urge Cuts in S & Ls' Broad Investment Powers; Office Expense Account (OEA) 2000; 32 Bundles of Press Clippings from Dominion Media Services Co., 1/22/2008-4/7/2008; Southern Women in Public Service Conference 2000; Water Projects Affecting Coal Transportation
  - Mass Mailings, 1/1/1994-12/31/1995 (Box 397)
    1994-1995 Mass Mailing; Campaign Information; Mass Mailings; Mailings; Mass Mailing File [binder]
  - Subject Files, 1/1/1992-12/31/1992 (Box 398)
    Atlantic Research; Belvoir: DOD move to Belvoir- Other Options; 6/1992; 103rd Congress; Belvoir: Belvoir Update: Toddy Puller, Belvoir Dep., PM, Robb; 6/30/1992; Alex Bigler- Equestrian Forge Co.; 1/1992; Chesapeake Div. (Navy) Restructuring; 2/3/1992; CIA Move Letters; CIT; Belvoir: Ft Belvoir/EPG Briefs; 3/1992; Aerospace Services International; Bow Industries (Tony O'Sullivan); CIA Relocation; 2/1992 (empty); Absentee Voting; 1/1992; Belvoir; George Mason BRPC Conference; 1/23-24/1992
  - Accepted Invitations, 3/25/1992-5/30/1992 (Box 399)
    68 envelopes arranged chronologically, some envelopes are empty.
  - Legislative Correspondence, 1/1/1986-12/31/1989 (Box 400)
    Co-Sponsored 100th Congress 1986; No Position 100th Congress 1987; Co-Signed Letters 100th Congress 1988; 1989 Tourism Caucus; Co-Signed Letters 100th Congress 1987; No Position 100th Congress 1988
  - Prints and Slides Senator John W. Warner, 1/1/1983-12/31/1993 (Box 401)
    Personal: Trips, Trips.88 (Group); 1988; Dan Quayle; Personal: Photos: Redskin Parade, Senator Warner, Joe Gibbs, Doug Williams; 1/1988; Files; List of in this drawer; Personal: Photographs: White House; 2/1/1984; Personal: Photos: Johnny's Graduation (empty); Personal: Photos: Senator with his Daughters at the Cape in Aug. 1987 (Mary sent these); Personal: Photographs: Trip to Soviet Union with Byrd Codel; Aug. 27-Sept 8/1985; Photos: Persian Gulf Trip with Senator Glenn; Untitled Envelope: Warner with President Reagan; Photo with Arafat, 1993; Personal: Photos: Inaugural Ball 1985; Misc. Photos; Untitled Envelope: Persian Gulf Photos; Dan Quayle; Untitled Envelope: Two people on a horse; Guigni Retirement: Senator John Warner R-225; Personal (Photos): Senators/Congressmen; Personal: Trips 1989, May thru Aug. 1989; Farnborough Air Show 1988; Personal: Photographs: Caricature for Alibi Club; Untitled Envelope: Playing tennis; Personal: Photos: Gorbachev's Visit to Us; Dec. 9/1987; White House: The First President Bush; Danny Thompson Memorial 1993; Hunting Photos/Horses; John Warner: misc. photos; Personal: Senate Restaurant 1990 Accounts; Personal: Photos; Reception in Honor of Chapman Cox, Asst. Sec. of Defense for Force Management and Personnel hosted by General Ernie Cheatham prior to Marine Corps Parade; 6/20/1986; Personal: Photos: Warner, Mary; Misc. Photos with Staff; Photos with the Dalai Lama
  - Presentations and Correspondence, 1/1/1980-12/31/1992 (Box 402)
    Senator John Warner Joint Resolutions 1990; 1990 Appropriations; Co-Signed, 1990; 1990 Speeches; Coker, Mary Phillips Fine Sporting Art, P.O. Box 141, Tryon, North Carolina 28782 [envelope]; Co-Signed, 1989
  - Scheduling and Accepted Invitations, 9/1/198-9/30/1988 (Box 403)
    28 envelopes
  - Statue of Liberty- Zumut Atoka County Supper File, Regional Offices Administrative Files, 1/1/1977-7/25/1986 (Box 404)